utilitytab.com 2017-12-24

# Privacy Policy

This Privacy Policy expresses the purposes and intent behind the information that is collected when you visit the UtilityTab website. Read it with care. If you continue in this endeavor to participate in our services, you will be held to the terms of this policy agreement. Personal Information Collected 

When you register to use www.utilitytab.com or any of the associated UtilityTab components, including but not limited to any special software packages, exclusive access to various restricted website areas, or customer support features, we may collect certain user specific, personally identifiable information. This information, including the likes of your name, physical address, email address, payment resources, and more, will be used, among other purposes, to record and process your site participation activities. When your desires for site participation require that you make payment to www.utilitytab.com , we may utilize a payment-processing merchant. Rest assured that any merchants we use will be required to operate under the same strict guidelines and criteria as are stipulated in this Privacy Policy. We refuse to knowingly collect personal information from persons under thirteen years of age.  
We give ever user the option of receiving useful product information, such as updates, virus alerts, and other associated product offerings, via opt-in permission based e-mail  
We value the trust of our users. Therefore, we seek to ensure your privacy. UtilityTab will never lease, rent, or sell the information that you provide to us.  
With the exception of the following conditions, UtilityTab refuses to share your personally identifiable information with any other party:  
· When specifically authorized by you to act in your behalf.   
· In response to legal demands.   
· When necessary to protect our interested from your actions.  
Concerning the issue of emails, you have the authority to unsubscribe from any of our automated email services.  
By willingly inputting personal information into any of our request forms, you are consenting to the terms of this www.utilitytab.com Privacy Policy. This includes an acceptance of our collection methods, our information disclosure methods, our information security methods, and the uses to which we put that information. 

Non-Personal Information Collection   
UtilityTab may also utilize automatic IP and service provider type information techniques. We utilize non-personal information on an aggregate basis. This means that we accumulate and process website activities based upon things like the number and frequency of site visitors, the length of each visit, page specifics, and more. UtilityTab may also employ cookie technology. This provides an additional means of tracking order activity, customer patterns, efforts to disrupt our services, and other site improvement valuables. Cookies are defined as text files that websites place on the hard drives of site visitors. You have, through your chosen Internet browser, the capacity to disable cookie functions. General Information Usage 

Along with the previously stated purposes, UtilityTab may also use the information we collect in the following ways  
· To process, validate and verify purchases.   
· To open and maintain a user specific support account.   
· To contact you when necessary for confirmation or verification of information accuracy.   
· To provide customized email content.   
· To notify you of changes to this policy.  
Links 

As a matter of general practice, and at our discretion as to the worth of the association, we may provide onsite links to third party websites. Such sites are not governed by this privacy policy. UtilityTab makes no representation about the methods for managing your personal information that are practiced on linked websites. We encourage you to check the privacy policy of each website at the beginning of your visit. Safety 

The personal information we collect about you is stored in limited access servers. UtilityTab maintains reasonable safeguards to shield the security of our computer servers. Furthermore, we apply special password and administrator identification methods as a deliberate means of further protecting your personally identifiable information. We retain personal information as long as is necessary to complete a user purchase transaction, a customer support call, or any other required account management process. Policy Changes 

Any time that we decide to update this Privacy Policy, we shall do so without need to notify you of that change. Check this page often. It is here that we will post all modifications to this Privacy Policy. 

Acceptance of Terms 

Use of UtilityTab services to access www.utilitytab.com , or use of UtilityTab products to accomplish personal or web related tasks requires that you agree to the terms, conditions, and practices that are listed in this UtilityTab Privacy Policy. You must now choose to exit our website, or to remain and abide by the terms of this Privacy Policy. UtilityTab is created by our company Honlyn (MCO) Limited. You may uninstall our software by following the instructions here Uninstall Instructions . Please reach us at help @ utilitytab.com . Our Company Name is Honlyn (MCO) Limited and our address is 34 Stanley Road Floor 15 Flat D Hong Kong
